<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Insanely Great President]]></title>
  <link href="http://insanelygreatpresident.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://insanelygreatpresident.com/"/>
  <updated>2015-01-17T10:18:50-08:00</updated>
  <id>http://insanelygreatpresident.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Mark Fussell]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Background on me]]></title>
    <link href="http://insanelygreatpresident.com/blog/background-on-me/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-17T18:15:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://insanelygreatpresident.com/blog/background-on-me</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>My name is Mark Fussell, and I have an unusually large set of skills.  Surviving Caltech, progressing through a total of ten+ startups,
writing multiple books, raising two daughters, building a relationship with a single wonderful woman over thirty years, becoming a patent expert, and
then a professional tennis player, that alone might sound pretty diverse.  But it  gets stranger: I am basically a trained financial
expert, a lawyer, a teacher of Robotics, Tennis, Programming, and technology in general,
a very good skater and skier, a highly capable marksman with both bullets and arrows, a lover of philosophy and government,
and a driver of many &ldquo;classes&rdquo; of vehicles (Motorcycle, Car, and Bus/MH).</p>

<p>All of the above is due to (a) a love of learning, and (b) an ability to focus and listen.  By this point, I am
an &ldquo;Execution Expert&rdquo; or what I also call &ldquo;A Delivery Boy&rdquo;: you let me know what you want&hellip; and I will deliver that
to you.  As long as it doesn&rsquo;t violate my morals, I can basically do almost anything.  I might need others to help
out, but I will find them as needed.</p>

<p>So that is most of the skinny on me.  You can find out some other information at:</p>

<ul>
<li> <a href="http://linkedin.com/in/markfussell">http://linkedin.com/in/markfussell</a></li>
<li> <a href="http://SlumsOfPaloAlto.com/">http://SlumsOfPaloAlto.com/</a></li>
<li> <a href="http://SupersonicFox.com/">http://SupersonicFox.com/</a></li>
</ul>


<p>and many other places on the internet or within my books.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
